[Zhijiang Capacity Infinite Tech (Zhejiang) Co., Ltd. & Zhejiang Yanhe Culture Tech Co., Ltd.]
Lord Su.
The limb joints of the two deceased
were broken off alive.
There are scratch marks from the fingers on the inside of the clay pot.
This means that when the victims were put into the pots,
they were not yet dead.
There are abrasions on the fingers.
They should be caused by struggling.
Breaking the joints.
From this point of view,
either the killer is born with supernatural strength,
or it really is a rat demon causing trouble.
It seems
that it's indeed somewhat different
from the method of making human swine.
Is the yellow soup in the urn
the same as the one in the clay pot last time?
Yes.
This pattern is indeed the same as last time.
It seems to be a serial murder case.
You just said there was another medicinal herb.
It's only found in Yeren Valley.
Yes.
It's called Jiangbian Yiwan Shui.
What about the other herbs?
They can all be bought in the city.
Check all the pharmacies in the city.
Let's go.
Baohetang Pharmacy.
In the past few days,
has your shop encountered
any suspicious strangers coming to buy herbs?
People who come here for herbs
are either sick themselves
or have a sick family member.
So they all look a bit strange.
Officer Su,
what kind of strange do you mean?
Stranger than the usual customers.
Like abnormal clothing or behavior.
I really can't remember clearly.
Forgive me.
This is the last pharmacy.
We don't have a single clue.
Wrong method.
Wasted effort.
What do you mean?
Memory Recovery Technique.
How about it?
Have you remembered anything?
I actually do remember something.
Three days ago,
there really was a strange customer who came for herbs.
That person
was tightly wrapped all over,
wearing a long black robe,
head covered in a hood,
and wearing a black veil.
Age,
appearance,
build?
Appearance,
height...
I couldn't really tell his age with the veil.
Also, the way he walked
was swaying.
It looked like there was something wrong with his legs.
What herbs did he buy?
Herbs?
There were too many.
And,
they were all tonics.
Your memory recovery method is really impressive.
I think
he will definitely come again in the next few days.
We just need to wait.
Maybe he'll go to another shop.
This isn't the only pharmacy in the city.
I'm sure he will only come to this one.
[Outside Baohetang Pharmacy]
Here he is.
What do you think?
Am I brilliant?
How on earth did you do that?
It was nothing, really.
I simply
bought all the medicinal herbs from pharmacies
within 10 miles.
This is the only place that has them.
You can do that?
Wow.
How much did that cost?
My way of doing things
is simple and direct.
I actually kind of admire you right now,
Shen Zhao, for squandering money for the people.
Follow him.
Let's go.
[Ruined temple]
It must be him.
Damn it.
He got away again.
Watch out.
Don't chase him.
We can't catch him.
I saw his true face.
What did he look like?
He had a rat head with sharp teeth,
terrifying prickly whiskers,
and looked absolutely horrifying.
He can change his shape
and possesses monstrous strength.
Could there really be
a rat spirit?
I doubt it.
Among street performers,
there's a martial art called the bone-shrinking skill.
It allows one to alter their bone positions at will
to shrink their body.
I think this rat spirit
is just a dwarf who knows the bone-shrinking skill.
He usually walks on stilts to deceive people.
Yes.
This...
Look at this.
This jade pendant
is smooth and warm.
It must be very expensive.
Moreover,
it has the character 'Xu' carved on it.
It must be their family name.
We can follow this clue to keep looking.
These are all the files of the wealthy families in Fangzhou.
I can't find the Xu family at all.
Maybe the Xu family is not from Fangzhou.
We can write to the Ministry of Revenue in Chang'an
and ask them to pull up
the household registers of all wealthy Xu families
to see if there are any clues.
Send it to the Ministry of Revenue?
Following normal procedures,
sending a letter from Fangzhou to Chang'an
and waiting for a reply
will take at least half a month.
It might take even longer.
By the time we get the news,
the murderer will have run far away.
Don't forget,
you have me.
It's so good to be rich.
Use the expedited relay post.
Deliver this letter and token
to Lord Li of the Ministry of Revenue in Chang'an.
Money alone
can't do this.
Remember,
don't reveal my identity.
Yes, Nephew.
Forgive me, Lord Ling.
I will take my leave.
Go quickly.
Help me! Help me!
A rat demon!
A big rat demon!
The rat demon is going to kill me!